Ms Janet DORNAN, MIET, BEng Warwickshire

Email: janet.d.coder@gmail.com Mobile: 07890 284497 Website: https://janet-dev.github.io
LinkedIn: https://github.com/janet-dev.github.io
BitHub: https://github.com/janet-dev

HTML	UI (industrial)	Python
CSS & Bootstrap	Git	Pandas & Flask
JavaScript	Ruby	Data & SQL

Ex-industrial UI engineer with over ten years' experience in the control industry, now expanding into programming and data analysis.

Highly motivated with excellent research skills, which enabled the building of a product-based website.

Team player, but also comfortable with working alone.

Skilled at multitasking, managing time effectively and prioritising tasks in line with the business.

Excellent at communication, both verbally and written, as well as confident with social media platforms.

Able to team manage and facilitate department meetings.

Possess advanced customer service skills in dealing with the public or business clients.

Well versed in mentoring both customers and clients on new departmental standards.

Career Professional Development

Code First Girls Introduction to Data and SQL Programming (incl. Tableau)

22 Apr – 10 Jun 2021 (remote with CFG)

ShowCode Athena Hackathon 2021 (incl. Pandas)

12 Apr – 23 Apr 2021 (Project Entry: https://devpost.com/software/rentaru)

Code First Girls Introduction to Python Programming (incl. Flask)

25 Feb – 15 Apr 2021 (remote with CFG)

freeCodeCamp Current Scientific Computing with Python Certification - Ongoing

Mar 2021 Basic HTML & CSS Mar 2021 Basic JavaScript

Code First Girls CFG: MOOCs Introduction to React.js / Dev. Cycle and Agile

22 Feb 2021 / 06 April 2021

Codecademy Learn Ruby

Feb 2021

Code First Girls Introduction to Web Development (incl. Bootstrap)

06 Oct – 24 Nov 2020 (remote with everis)

InsideSherpa Commonwealth Bank Virtual Internship Participant - Careers in Tech

Jul – Sep 2020 Design (UX/UI), Software Engineering, Cyber Security,

Data Science and Analytics, AI / Robotics

codebar Student member

Aug 2020 - present

Office Skills

- Microsoft Office (Microsoft Excel, Access, Word, PowerPoint), Open Office, Libre Office
- Tableau for visual data analysis
- Graphics / HMI (Human Machine Interface) / UI design packages used within the control system industry
- Windows, OS X and Linux operating systems (Ubuntu/Mint)
- WordPress for self hosted website building
- Social media for marketing Instagram, Facebook, Pinterest, TikTok, YouTube
- Canva for marketing and branding
- Manual data analysis within a small bakery

Employment History

09/2016 - Present	Non-coding roles	Various
01/2016 - 04/2016	Field Services Engineer (*HMI)	Schneider Electric (Invensys UK)
01/2012 – 10/2014	Field Services Engineer (*HMI)	Invensys Systems Nigeria
02/2010 - 01/2012	Non-coding roles	Various
01/2009 – 01/2010	Graphics Engineer (*HMI)	Honeywell Process Systems
08/2002 – 12/2008	Applications Engineer (*HMI)	GroupCytek

^{*}HMI – Human Machine Interface (UI / GUI / Industrial Control Graphics)

Education:

University of Oxford PGCert in Software and Systems Security

Apr 2015 - Oct 2018

RGIT (RGU), Aberdeen BEng(Hons) in Electronic and Electrical Engineering

Strathearn School, Belfast NIGCE: Maths – B, English – B

Languages: Basic: Russian, German, French

Professional Memberships: Member of the Institution of Engineering and Technology

Member of the Institute of Physics

Non-Coding Interests: Designing and marketing own handmade artisan jewellery

Keen allotment owner, growing vegetables and tortoise food

Producing kombucha, kefir and farmer's cheese